Asada...
Shino Asada...
Thank
you.
How do you feel?
When you're hurt, you'll
find a regretful feeling.
How do you feel?
A painless pain.
I know that the strong strength will be?
Oh
We'll pay you back, though.
Ten thousand?
I don't have that much money on me.
Well, go withdraw it, then.
No. Huh?
You heard.
I said no.
I'm not giving you guys any money.
You bitch.
We'll do this the hard way.
Get out of the way.
I want to go.
Mm-hmm.
Bang.
Poor Asada.
You know my big brother?
Well, he's got a buttload
of these model guns.
Wouldn't it be cool if
I brought some to class?
I know you like guns, especially pistols.
Uh-oh, someone's gonna hurl.
Remember when you blew
chunks in class and fainted?
Oh, God, that stank like ass for days.
All you have to do is give us your
money and we'll let you go home.
Don't you, Anna?
I mean, you look like hell.
Officer!
The girl's getting mugged in the alley!
Hurry!
Bitch!
Asura, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, Shinkawa.
Thanks for that.
So I heard what happened the other
day you went on quite the rampage.
Yeah but for a strategy
it was a fail I mean we
started the op with six
and lost four by the end.
Of it if that's the outcome of
an ambush we set up it's not
much of a win you know you
were pretty Rad though you know
that behemoth guy with the
minigun he was kind of a legend in
the game because he never bought
it in a squad fight before.
Yeah?
I had no idea he was that good.
I never really saw his
rankings in B .O .B.
His days were numbered.
I mean, no matter how
powerful a minigun is?
Carrying 500 rounds of ammo.
pushes you over the weight
limit so you can't run.
And since B .O .B.'s a
solo encounter battle,
he was easy pickings
for a sniper like you.
Still, with that gun, he's pretty much
invincible as long as he's with a good squad.
The minigun should be banned.
If we're talking about banning weapons,
don't forget, some people
think my Hecate's a cheat, too.
As its owner, I have to admit, using
it does have its own special problems.
Wish I had problems like that.
So, what are your plans
for the next B .O .B.?
I'm definitely entering.
I did my homework and have most of the info
of the top 20 players from the last one.
And I've got my Hecate now.
With her in my hands,
I'm sure I can kill...
I mean, crack the higher ranks.
If I can take out all my enemies and
prove I'm the strongest, I'll be free.
Anne.
Asada, you're amazing.
Having that awesome gun is one thing.
But you were also smart enough to put your
points on strength stats
so you could use it.
I'm the one who got you into GGO.
but I've been totally left behind.
That is so not true.
In the last qualifier, you made it all
the way to the semi-finals, remember?
Whatever.
An AGI build only gets you so far in GGO.
A good gun helps too.
I spent points on the wrong stat.
Don't get so down about that stuff.
Sign up for B .O .B.
and see what happens.
Nah, no point. I just die.
Oh, hmm.
Hey, how are your studies coming along?
You still want to be a doctor?
Yeah, it is the family business.
I promised my dad I'd go to med
school, so it's a done deal.
Stuck with it now.
Well, what about cram school and the GED?
Are those going okay?
Oh, yeah.
It's going great.
I'm maintaining the same rank
I had when I was at school.
Staying sharp, ma 'am.
Locked and loaded.
Roger that.
The reason I asked is because
you're always online when I log on.
That's why I was a little worried.
If you're online that
much, when do you study?
I do most of my studying during the
day, and I take lots of breaks too.
You must be making tons of cash if
you're diving all the time like that.
I'm not making that much.
Solo hunting's impossible
for AGI Builds these days.
Oh, well, you're doing great if you're
earning enough for the connection fee.
Uh-oh, it's late.
Sorry, I have to get going now.
Oh, okay.
Hey, are you still making
dinner for yourself?
I'd love to try more of
your cooking someday.
Huh?
Oh, sure. Okay.
It's just, I think I need
to get better at it first.
Thanks for the tea.
And thanks, I mean thank
you, for saving me.
You were pretty cool.
I wish I could always
be there to protect you.
Hey, if you want, I can
walk you home every day.
I mean, if you want.
Oh, no, no, that's okay.
I'll be fine.
It's the only way I'll get stronger.
What a day.
I can do this.
I don't remember what dad looked like.
I remember hearing he died
in a car accident, though.
Sometime before I turned two.
After the accident, my
mom and I left Tokyo.
We went to go live with her parents.
It was peaceful there for both of us.
And then, one day, that
peace was shattered.
Put the money in the bag, goddammit!
And don't hit the alarm, or else...
Mommy...
Come on, don't just stand there!
Start filling it up!
Let's go, move it!
Okay, sure.
I told him not to!
You heard me!
Let's go, bitch!
Fill it up or you get it, too!
Give me the money now or
I'm gonna kill her next!
I swear I'll do it!
YOU LITTLE GIVE IT STUCK
YOU BRATS! LET'S GO!
LET'S GO OF MY GUN!
Oh, my God.
No!
I look awful.
Somebody.
Somebody. Anybody.
Save me.
Wait, what?
You're kidding, you're quitting ALO?
No, I'll just be gone
for a couple of days.
I'll convert back after that. But why?
Well, actually, it's complicated.
There's this other virtual
MMO that I need to check out.
Need to, huh?
You've done this before
and just used new accounts.
Why not for this one, too?
I mean, if you convert,
your items will be reset.
Why would you want to do that?
Well, it's like a favor for
that guy from the government.
I guess if Mr.
Kikuoka is asking you
to, you can't say no.
I don't know what it is about that man.
But there's a part of me that
still has a hard time trusting him.
Yeah, I'm not too sure
I can trust him either.
Just get back as soon as you can!
This is our home, and it's
not the same without you.
Don't worry, I'll be back
in ALO before you know it.
I'll just dive into Gun Gale
online for a couple days,
see what's going on, and that's that.
I'm 99 % sure the Death
Gun story's a hoax.
Probably someone trolling.
You can't kill someone in the real
world from the virtual anymore.
I know that's impossible.
This is real power, real strength.
Let your fear carve one
name into your brains.
The name I share with
this weapon, Death Gun.
But there's still that 1
% chance it could be true.
That's why I'm here.
Hello, anyone here? Yep.
What's going on, Kirigaya?
Ms.
Aki, it's nice to see you again.
Holy - Whoa, you finally
got some meat on you.
You could use some filling out, though.
You sure you're eating right?
Yeah, I'm eating, I'm eating.
Wait a minute, what are you doing here?
Your friend in the suit and
glasses told me about your mission.
He said something about
you going into a virtual
network and doing some
reconnaissance or something.
I can't believe he'd ask you.
I mean, you've only been back for a year.
Anyway, he found out I was the one
who was in charge of your rehab.
So he asked me to keep an eye
on your monitors while you dive.
They took me off my normal
shift and everything.
The head nurse wasn't happy,
but what can she do about it?
If the government wants
something, they're gonna get it.
Well, I guess you and me are
back together again, huh?
Yeah, thanks for being here.
So it's just us today,
no Ki-Kuoka? Mm-hmm.
He asked me to give you a message, though.
Email your reports to
me at the usual address.
Your fee and expenses will be
paid when you finish the mission,
so please don't forget
to send me an invoice.
P .S.
Just because you're alone with a pretty
nurse, you're still on the clock.
Try to keep those hormones
of yours under control.
Uh, if it's okay, I'd like to
connect to the network now.
Yeah, sure.
It's all set up.
Okay, hot stuff. Strip! Why?
For the electrodes.
Oh, don't be shy.
I've seen all your goodies before.
Actually, can I just take off my shirt?
Mm-hmm.
There.
You're good to go.
Well, here I go.
Wish me luck.
I don't see this taking me
more than four or five hours.
You got it.
And don't you worry about
your body while you're gone.
I'll keep a close eye on it. Thanks.
I feel better already.
Link, start!
Yeah, I'm doing great.
I'm used to the school now, and
I've made some friends, too.
I'm fine, really.
I've only had a couple
panic attacks, that's all.
Yeah, Grandpa, I will.
Don't you catch any colds, either.
I'll come home for winter break.
Me too. Bye.
Ever since that day, whenever
I see a gun, I freak out.
If I see a picture of one, or see one
on TV, I'm guaranteed a panic attack.
I came to Tokyo for high school,
thinking if I got far enough
away from home, it'd help.
But it didn't.
One day,
Shinkawa told me about Gun Gale Online,
and I thought it could work
as a kind of therapy for me.
And in a way, it worked.
As Sinon, when I'm holding a gun or
when someone's drawing down on me,
I can handle it.
I figure the stronger Sinon gets, the
stronger I'll get in the real world.
So I keep fighting with my Akati too.
Hoping it'll help me kick this phobia?
Winning the next bullet
of bullets will cure me!
I know it will.
It has to.
Link start
Zexeed and Tarako haven't
logged on for a while.
It's been like a month.
If anyone's got their contact info in
the real world, hook us up with it.
Dude, if no one's heard from them
this long, they're gone for good.
We know the date and time they
were shot by Death Gun, though.
So all we have to do is check if any
VR MMO players died around that time,
and we'll know what happened to them.
Yeah, but if they lived alone, maybe
no one's found their bodies yet.
We already asked the cops,
but they're not talking.
We even sent emails to Zaskar about
him, but all they sent back was the old?
sorry, we never share our
user's personal info crap.
I hate to say it,
but the only way to be sure they were killed
is for one of us to sacrifice himself.
So tomorrow at 11.30pm,
I'm going to wait for Death Gun
at the Glock and Central Bank.
And just so he knows it's me,
I'll have a red rose on my chest.
Shoot me, Death Gun, I dare you!
Aw, dude, you'll be a hero.
But you better post your real name and
address, otherwise, what's the point?
Oh, do a public dive in
an internet cafe, man!
Or whatever.
I want to be strong, strong,
I want to be proud of the sadness.
I've never seen a
change
in my past.
I've never seen a lot of my eyes.
I want you to be strong, so strong!.
I want you to be willing to go!.
With a deep deep heart and deep!.
I don't think you can be able
to be able to be honest?.
Next time, GGO.